# **Zakir Raza**

Front-End Developer

## **Summary**

Experienced web developer adept in all stages of advanced web development. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

# **Experience**

Front end Developer- Mar, 2024 – April 2024

#### GDSC, Karachi

As an Internee Front-end Web Developer at GDSC, my role involved crafting visually engaging and user-friendly websites to captivate both our clients and their audiences. I worked closely with our design and development teams to bring concepts to life.

#### Front-end Developer - Jul, 2024 - Aug, 2024

#### NextGenDev, Karachi

As an Internee at NextGenDev, I utilized HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript to develop visually engaging and user-friendly websites that captivated both our clients and their audiences. I worked in close collaboration with our design and development teams to transform ideas into reality.

### **Education**

**Bachelors in Computer Science - September 2022 - Present** 

Muhammad Ali Jinnah University, Karachi

Web Development - May, 2024 - Present

Saylani IT Mass Training Program, Karachi

### **Contact**

**Phone:** +92 3293271727

E-Mail:

zaakiraza110@gmail.com

**Portfolio:**https://zakirraza 110.github.io/Portfolio/

**GitHub:**https://github.com/Zakirraza110

### **Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Git
- SOL
- JavaScript